BRYAN KHAMLY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER \$\ 714-383-2580

• DETAILS •

714-383-2580 bryankhamly@gmail.com

· LINKS ·

Portfolio

Linkedin

SKILLS

Unity

C#

Agile

Python

JavaScript

SQL

C++

REST

Google Firebase

PROFILE

I'm a reliable programmer who's worked in the video game industry. I enjoy working in an Agile environment and I take the initiative to create tools to help designers on the project. I enjoy working on game development projects, and expanding my knowledge on new software engineering technologies.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Lead Game Programmer at Team73

2021 - 2023

Core Gameplay Systems, and Multiplayer on an open world procedurally generated adventure sandbox. Project on hold looking for animators and funding.

Lead Software Engineer at One Tap Studios

May 2020 — October 2020

- Lead and managed a team of people to create a multi-player survival game
- Collaborated with artists to create gameplay systems and building mechanics
- Interested investors include PlayVentures, Tencent and Gamigo

Software Engineer at Broken Circle Studios

October 2019 — April 2020

- Full stack engineer for mobile and PC games
- · Created executive dashboards to administrate user data
- · Performance optimizations and PC to console porting
- Communicated in teams to exceed client expectations
- Titles worked on include Osiris New Dawn

★ AWARDS

LCAD Hot Jam - Winner

March 2021 — March 2021

- Collaborated in a team of 5 to create a video game following a theme in 5 days called Hot Pot Rampage
- · Lead Programmer, created core gameplay systems and AI
- Won 1st place, with Best Art Award and Community's Pick

UCLA LAHacks - Best Unity Hack

March 2018 — April 2018

- Managed a team of 3 to create an action-packed virtual reality video game called Invasion
- · Created artificial intelligence for characters and integrated project resources

EDUCATION

Game Programming, Norco College

February 2018 — October 2019

■ REFERENCES

References available upon request